Register of the Ernest Lundeen Papers, 1860-1944
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1894-1942
  - 1899-1925. Mostly constituent mail; some correspondence with clients and friends, arranged alphabetically
    - Hall, Bert (Box 80., Folder 1)
    - Hall, Howard L. (Folder 2)
    - Hall, James H. (Folder 3)
    - Hallberg, Elmer (Folder 4)
    - Hallman, G. F. (Folder 5)
    - Halls, J. C. (Folder 6)
    - Hammar, Albert (Folder 7)
    - Hammer, Henry (Folder 8)
    - Hammond, W. S. (Folder 9)
    - Hanks, Maude N. (Folder 10)
    - Hanley, M. F. (Folder 11)
    - Hanna, Kristen (Folder 12)
    - Harcourt Savings Bank (Folder 13)
    - Hardwood Manufacturing Company (Folder 14)
    - Harries, W. H. (Folder 15)
    - Harris, W. D. (Folder 16)
    - Harrison, J. G. (Folder 17)
    - Hawkinson, Carl and Frances (Folder 18)
    - Hawley, Ella S. (Folder 19)
    - Hayes, R. M. (Folder 20)
    - Heebner, F. A. (Folder 21)
    - Helgeson, Henry T. (Folder 22)
    - Hempstead, E. A. (Folder 23)
    - Hendee, M., Mrs. (Folder 24)
    - Hendee, Simeon (Folder 25)
    - Hendricks, Edwin A. (Folder 26)
    - Hendrickson, P. M. (Folder 27)
    - Hennepin County Savings Bank (Folder 28)
    - Hennepin County Woman Suffrage Association (Folder 29)
    - Herbst, Edith M. (Folder 30)
    - Hermes, Joseph M. (Folder 31)
    - Hermion Lodge, Knights of Pythias (Folder 32)
    - Heywood Manufacturing Company (Folder 33)
    - Hillman, N. S. (Folder 34)
    - Hinch, Frederick M. (Folder 35)
    - Hind, Robert (Folder 36)
    - Hitchcock, Reuben W. (Folder 37)
    - Holmes, G. D. (Folder 38)
    - Holmgren, C. J. (Folder 39)
    - Holmquist-Hansen concert tour, 1915 (Folder 40)
    - Horn, Charles L. (Folder 41)
    - Houck, Stanley B. (Folder 42)
    - Houck, William F. (Folder 43)
    - Houliston, John (Folder 44)
    - Hughes, Hugh (Folder 45)
    - Humpfner, Hilda (Folder 46)
    - Hurd, Ethel E. (Folder 47)
    - Hurley, Patrick (Folder 48)
    - Huttner Printing Company (Folder 49)
    - I unsorted (Folder 50)
    - J unsorted (Folder 51)
    - Jackman, Jerome (Box 81., Folder 1)
    - Jacob, Alexander (Folder 2)
    - Jacobson, Arthur (Folder 3)
    - Jaroscak, Paul (Folder 4)
    - Jayne, Trafford (Folder 5)
    - Jenson, Arthur C. (Folder 6)
    - Jepson, Lowell (Folder 7)
    - Jerdee, M. E. (Folder 8)
    - Jerome, W. M. (Folder 9)
    - Johnson unsorted (Folder 10)
    - Johnson, A. G. (Folder 11)
    - Johnson, Adolph E. L. (Folder 12)
    - Johnson, Betty (Folder 13)
    - Johnson, C. E. (Folder 14)
    - Johnson, Charles (Folder 15)
    - Johnson, Elmer (Folder 16)
    - Johnson, Harold E. (Folder 17)
    - Johnson, Henrietta (Folder 18)
    - Johnson, J. Fred (Folder 19)
    - Johnson, J. William (Folder 20)
    - Johnson, John A. (Folder 21)
    - Johnson, Royal C. (Folder 22)
    - Jones, David P. (Folder 23)
    - Jorgenson, Carl (Folder 24)
    - K unsorted (Folder 25)
    - Kipping, T. S. (Folder 26)
    - Kjorlang, Melchoir N. S. (Folder 27)
    - Knutson, George (Folder 28)
    - Knutson, Harold (Folder 29)
    - Koschel, Gustave (Folder 30)
    - Kulander, J. P. (Folder 31)
    - Kylander, A. N. (Folder 32)
    - L unsorted (Folder 33)
    - La Doucre, A. J. (Box 82., Folder 1)
    - La Follette, Robert M. (Folder 2)
    - Lager, Martin F. (Folder 3)
    - Lamson, Frank B. (Folder 4)
    - Langes, Leona (Folder 5)
    - Larson, A. G. (Folder 6)
    - Larson, Gustaf (Folder 7)
    - Lassiter, Jesse M. (Folder 8)
    - Lincoln, Levi T. (Folder 9)
    - Lind, C. A. (Folder 10)
    - Lind, John C. (Folder 11)
    - Linden, Henning (Folder 12)
    - Linden, Philip T. (Folder 13)
    - Lindholm, J. W. (Folder 14)
    - Lindquist, Ernest P. (Folder 15)
    - Lindquist, Fred E. (Folder 16)
    - Lindstrom, Emil A. (Folder 17)
    - Lindstrom, John A. (Folder 18)
    - Lochner, Louis P. (Folder 19)
    - Long, Thomas J. (Folder 20)
    - Lundeen family (Folder 21)
    - Lundeen, David (Folder 22)
    - Lundeen, Joel (Folder 23)
    - M unsorted (Folder 24-28)
    - McDonald, Mary E. (Box 83., Folder 1)
    - McElmeel, Owen P. (Folder 2)
    - McEwen, William E. (Folder 3)
    - MacGregor, William E. (Folder 4)
    - McReavy, Vernon L. (Folder 5)
    - Mann, James R. (Folder 6)
    - Martin, G. W. (Folder 7)
    - Martin, H. B. (Folder 8)
    - Martin, L. W. (Folder 9)
    - Martinson, Oscar (Folder 10)
    - Masons (Folder 11)
    - Matson, A. S. (Folder 12)
    - Maynard, H. S. (Folder 13)
    - Merz, Ed (Folder 14)
    - Methven, Theron (Folder 15)
    - Michaels, Oliver (Folder 16)
    - Milligan, John W. (Folder 17)
    - Miller, Emma D. (Folder 18)
    - Miller-Davis Printing Company (Folder 19)
    - Mitchell, William (Folder 20)
    - Moe, Henry (Folder 21)
    - Mohammed, Abdul (Folder 22)
    - Montgomery, R. B. (Folder 23)
    - N unsorted (Folder 24-25)
    - Nagle, John W. (Folder 26)
    - National Voters League (Folder 27)
    - Neale, Charles C. (Folder 28)
    - Nelson, Arnold, Mrs. (Folder 29)
    - Nelson, Emil A. (Folder 30)
    - Nelson, Frank (Folder 31)
    - Nelson, Gust F. (Folder 32)
    - Nelson, Knut (Folder 33)
    - Nelson, Peter A. (Folder 34)
    - Newhall, William B. (Folder 35)
    - Newton, George W. (Folder 36)
    - Nix, W. J. (Box 84., Folder 1)
    - Nolan, Daniel (Folder 2)
    - Nolan, W. I. (Folder 3)
    - Nord, Victor W. (Folder 4)
    - Nordstrom, O. E. (Folder 5)
    - Norman, Charles W. (Folder 6)
    - Norton, Sewald P. (Folder 7)
    - Norton, W. E. (Folder 8)
    - Nyberg, Knudt (Folder 9)
    - Nye, Frank M. (Folder 10)
    - Nygren Printing Company (Folder 11)
    - O unsorted (Folder 12-13)
    - P unsorted (Folder 14-15)
    - P unsorted (Box 85., Folder 1)
    - Painter, Carl W. (Folder 2)
    - Parkhill, T. E. (Folder 3)
    - Passmore, Charlotte (Folder 4)
    - A. R. Patterson Post, Veterans of Foreign Wars (Folder 5)
    - Penniman, D. C. (Folder 6)
    - Perl, Frederick (Folder 7)
    - Perry, Andrew (Folder 8)
    - Perrizo, L. (Folder 9)
    - Persinger, Floyd T. (Folder 10)
    - Peterson unsorted (Folder 11)
    - Peterson, C. O. (Folder 12)
    - Peterson, J. A. (Folder 13)
    - Peterson, James A. (Folder 14)
    - Peterson, J. E. (Folder 15)
    - Petrain, A. H. (Folder 16)
    - Phelan, Raymond W. (Folder 17)
    - Phelps, Edmund J. (Folder 18)
    - Pinchot, Gifford (Folder 19)
    - Polk, R. L. (Folder 20)
    - Pool, Harry R. (Folder 21)
    - Pooley, George T., Mrs. (Folder 22)
    - Powell, John (Folder 23)
    - Powers, Fred M. (Folder 24)
    - Prescott, Henry R. (Folder 25)
    - Preus, J. A. O. (Folder 26)
    - Price, Bertram J. (Folder 27)
    - Probstfield, J. T. (Folder 28)
    - Purdy, E. A. (Folder 29)
    - Pushkin Club (Folder 30)
    - Q unsorted (Folder 31)
    - Quarnstrom, Mathilda (Folder 32)
    - R unsorted (Folder 33-34)
    - R unsorted (Box 86., Folder 1)
    - Rahn, A. A. D. (Folder 2)
    - Ramee, Per (Folder 3)
    - Rankin, Jeannette (Folder 4)
    - Rasmussen Publishing Company (Folder 5)
    - Rawson, Charles A. (Folder 6)
    - Reed, Frank C. (Folder 7)
    - Regan, William M. (Folder 8)
    - Reid, James G. (Folder 9)
    - Rendell, W. H. (Folder 10)
    - Rice, Cushman A. (Folder 11)
    - Richter, Dan E. (Folder 12)
    - Rifenberg, Jennie (Folder 13)
    - Rines, Henry (Folder 14)
    - Ringlund, G. A. (Folder 15)
    - Ringstrom, Hugo (Folder 16)
    - Roan, Carl M. (Folder 17)
    - Robbins, Madge (Folder 18)
    - Robinson, Annie M. (Folder 19)
    - Rogers, A. F. (Folder 20)
    - Rogers, William F. (Folder 21)
    - Roof, Nora (Folder 22)
    - Roos, Hilma (Folder 23)
    - Rorem, Allen T. (Folder 24)
    - Rose, W. H. (Folder 25)
    - Rosen, J. A. (Folder 26)
    - Rost, Ernest C. (Folder 27)
    - Royal Typewriter Company (Folder 28)
    - Ruberg, May, Mrs. (Folder 29)
    - Rudgren, Gust (Folder 30)
    - Russell, Thomas (Folder 31)
    - Ryberg, C. E. (Folder 32)
    - S unsorted (Folder 33-34)
    - Samuels, Anna Lundeen (Box 87., Folder 1)
    - Sandy, Benjamin (Folder 2)
    - Schall, Thomas D. (Folder 3)
    - Scheuer, Jack J. (Folder 4)
    - Schlener Stationery Company (Folder 5)
    - Schmahl, Julius A. (Folder 6)
    - Schmidt, Peter (Folder 7)
    - Schuller, Ruby N. (Folder 8)
    - Seaberg, S. P. (Folder 9)
    - Seal, Earl G. (Folder 10)
    - Sexton, Lizzie (Folder 11)
    - Shadegg, J. C. (Folder 12)
    - Sheldon, W. D. (Folder 13)
    - Shellman, W. F. (Folder 14)
    - Shogren, Axel G. (Folder 15)
    - Simons, Henry L. (Folder 16)
    - Skidmore, Wallace G. (Folder 17)
    - Smith, C. L. (Folder 18)
    - Smith, Charles Sumner (Folder 19)
    - L. C. Smith and Brothers (Folder 20)
    - Smith, Walter J. (Folder 21)
    - Snyder, G. F. (Folder 22)
    - South Side State Bank (Folder 23)
    - Spanish War Veterans (Folder 24)
    - Sperry, Marvin Gates (Folder 25)
    - Steenerson, Halvor (Folder 26)
    - Stiles, George C. (Folder 27)
    - Sulzer, William (Folder 28)
    - Swanson, C. O. (Folder 29)
    - Swanson, Oscar (Folder 30)
    - Swedenborg (Folder 31)
    - Swenson, Jennie (Folder 32)
    - Swift, Linton B. (Folder 33)
    - T unsorted (Folder 34-35)
    - Henry Taylor Jr. and Company (Folder 36)
    - Edward Thompson Company (Folder 37)
    - Thompson, Lynn (Folder 38)
    - Thompson, Richard C. (Folder 39)
    - Thompson, W. B. (Folder 40)
    - Thompson, William Hale (Folder 41)
    - Thornton, Eric L. (Box 88., Folder 1)
    - Tilson, John Q. (Folder 2)
    - Titus, Richard E. (Folder 3)
    - Torelle, A. N. (Folder 4)
    - Townsend, J. R. (Folder 5)
    - Tracey, W. E. (Folder 6)
    - Tri State Telephone Company (Folder 7)
    - Trickett, W. P. (Folder 8)
    - Trimble, South (Folder 9)
    - Trollhattan Lodge, Order of Vasa (Folder 10)
    - Turner, George W. (Folder 11)
    - Twenty-five, Committee of (Folder 12)
    - U, V unsorted (Folder 13)
    - Van Deusen, William P. (Folder 14)
    - Van Hook, L. S. (Folder 15)
    - Van Lear, Thomas (Folder 16)
    - Van Sant, Samuel R. (Folder 17)
    - Van Slyke, Carl C. (Folder 18)
    - Van Slyke, James R. (Folder 19)
    - W unsorted (Folder 20)
    - W unsorted (Box 89., Folder 1-2)
    - Walsh, James A. (Folder 3)
    - Walton, Percy A. (Folder 4)
    - Wagner, Emma R. (Folder 5)
    - Warner, Ernest E. (Folder 6)
    - Warner's Hardware (Folder 7)
    - Waterman, Eva (Folder 8)
    - Weikert, Claire I. (Folder 9)
    - Weirner, Maurice (Folder 10)
    - Wesley Methodist Episcopal Church (Folder 11)
    - Weston, Eleanor (Folder 12)
    - Whipps, S. S. (Folder 13)
    - White, Harrison (Folder 14)
    - White, M. H. (Folder 15)
    - Widen, Ed and Esther Lundeen (Folder 16)
    - Widen, J. E. (Folder 17)
    - Wilson, E. W. (Folder 18)
    - Wilson, J. Stanley (Folder 19)
    - Windrum, J. J. (Folder 20)
    - Winter, T. G. (Folder 21)
    - Women's Cooperative Alliance (Folder 22)
    - Wood, Loren N. (Folder 23)
    - Woods, Frank P. (Folder 24)
    - Woody, Norman C. (Folder 25)
    - Wyer, R. E. (Folder 26)
    - Wyman, J. F. (Folder 27)
    - Wynn, F. C. (Folder 28)
    - X, Y, Z, unsorted (Folder 29)
    - Yawman and Erbe Manufacturing Company (Folder 30)
    - Youngdahl, E. W. (Folder 31)
    - Youngdahl, Peter J. (Folder 32)
    - Youngstown, Ohio speech (Folder 33)
  - 1917-1918. Constituent mail for or against war and conscription, arranged alphabetically
    - Constituent mail against war
      - A - B (Box 90., Folder 1)
      - C - E (Folder 2)
      - F - J (Folder 3)
      - K - M (Box 91., Folder 1)
      - M - O (Folder 2)
      - P - R (Folder 3)
      - S - V (Folder 4)
    - Constituent mail for war
      - Petitions (Box 92., Folder 1)
      - A - B (Folder 2)
      - C (Folder 3)
      - D - G (Folder 4)
      - H (Folder 5)
      - I - K (Folder 6)
      - L - N (Box 93., Folder 1)
      - N (Folder 2)
      - O - P (Folder 3)
      - R - S (Folder 4)
      - T - Z (Box 94., Folder 1)
    - Conscription
      - Petitions (Folder 2)
      - A - H (Folder 3)
      - I - P (Folder 4)
      - R - Z (Folder 5)
  - 1937. United States. Supreme Court. Constituent mail about the "packing scheme," arranged whether for or against and further divided into categories of mail from persons in Minnesota and out of state
    - General (Box 95., Folder 1)
    - Increasing members, against (Folder 2-7)
    - Increasing members, against (Box 96., Folder 1-7)
    - Increasing members, against (Box 97., Folder 1-4)
    - Increasing members, against (Box 98., Folder 1-4)
    - Increasing members, against (Box 99., Folder 1-3)
    - Increasing members, against (Box 100., Folder 1-4)
    - Increasing members, against (out of state addresses) (Folder 5)
    - Increasing members, against (out of state addresses) (Box 101., Folder 1-2)
    - Increasing members, for (Folder 3-6)
  - 1937-1939. Constituent mail arranged alphabetically by subject or name of legislative bill
    - General (Box 102., Folder 1)
    - Accident prevention (Folder 2)
    - Air Commerce bill (Folder 3)
    - Airships (Folder 4)
    - Anti-lynching bill (Folder 5)
    - Argentine agreement (Folder 6)
    - Aviation and airports (Folder 7)
    - Barbers bill (Folder 8)
    - Black, Hugo (Folder 9)
    - Branch banking (Folder 10)
    - Chain store tax (Folder 11)
    - Child Labor bill (Folder 12)
    - Civil liberties (Folder 13)
    - Civilian Conservation Corps (Folder 14)
    - Co-operatives (Folder 15)
    - Cotton (Folder 16)
    - Duluth Superior Bridge (Folder 17)
    - Economy (Folder 18)
    - Education, Adult civic (Folder 19)
    - Fair Trade bill (Folder 20)
    - Farm bill (Folder 21)
    - Farm Credit Act of 1937 (Box 103., Folder 1)
    - Farm legislation (Folder 2)
    - Farm tenancy (Folder 3)
    - Federal aid for highway construction (Folder 4)
    - Federal Arts bill (Folder 5)
    - Federal employees legislation (Folder 6)
    - Federal Reserve Banks (Folder 7)
    - Federal Trade Commission (Folder 8)
    - Flood Control Act (Folder 9)
    - Food and Drug bill (Folder 10)
    - Grain standards (Folder 11)
    - Grasshopper menace (Folder 12)
    - Highway appropriations (Folder 13)
    - Hops bill (Folder 14)
    - Housing Act (Folder 15)
    - Indian affairs (Folder 16)
    - Jewish problem (Folder 17)
    - Military problem (Folder 18)
    - Money (Folder 19)
    - Munitions bills (Folder 20)
    - National Labor Relations Board (Folder 21)
    - Naval appropriations (Folder 22)
    - Neutrality
      - General (Box 104., Folder 1-2)
      - Mandatory, for (Folder 3)
      - Mandatory, against (Folder 4)
    - Noxious weed problem (Folder 5)
    - Oil and gas taxes (Folder 6)
    - Old age pension
      - General (Folder 7)
      - Townsend Plan (Folder 8)
    - Pettengill bill (long and short hauling) (Folder 9)
    - Philippine Islands (Folder 10)
    - Post office clerks (Folder 11)
    - Postal employees legislation (Folder 12)
    - Postal substitutes (Folder 13)
    - Postmasters bill (Box 105., Folder 1)
    - Processing tax (Folder 2)
    - Public Works Administration (Folder 3)
    - Public Works and Relief Standards Act (Folder 4)
    - Puerto Rico (Folder 5)
    - Railroad labor legislation (Folder 6)
    - Railroad Retirement Act (Folder 7)
    - Reciprocal trade
      - General (Folder 8)
      - Government policy (Folder 9)
      - Labor's opinion (Folder 10)
      - Texts and agreements (Folder 11)
    - Reciprocal Trade Act (Folder 12)
    - Reclamation (Folder 13)
    - Recovery Act (Box 106., Folder 1)
    - Relief appropriations (Folder 2)
    - Resettlement
      - General (Folder 3)
      - Eveleth, Minnesota (Folder 4)
    - Resources (Folder 5)
    - Riverways and parks (Folder 6)
    - Rural Electrification Act (Folder 7)
    - Scrap iron and steel exports (Folder 8)
    - Sit down strikes (Folder 9)
    - Social Security Act (Folder 10)
      - Amendments (Folder 11)
      - Lundeen-Dunn bill (Folder 12)
      - Unemployment insurance (Folder 13)
    - Tax evasion (Folder 14)
    - Tax, undivided profit (Folder 15)
    - Taxation
      - General (Folder 16)
      - Liquor (Folder 17)
      - Processing (Folder 18)
      - Retroactive (Folder 19)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 107., Folder 1)
    - Trade (Folder 2)
    - Train (cars) limit bill (Folder 3)
    - U unsorted (Folder 4)
    - Unemployment (Folder 5)
    - United States District Judges
      - Moonan, Joseph (Folder 6)
      - Nyquist, E. V. (Folder 7)
      - Peterson, Harry H. (Folder 8)
      - Schleiter, C. W. (Folder 9)
      - Sullivan, George (Folder 10)
      - Uhich, Lester (Folder 11)
    - Universal Service bill
      - General (Folder 12)
      - Against (Folder 13)
    - Veterans (Folder 14)
    - W unsorted (Folder 15)
    - Wagner Act (Folder 16)
    - War
      - General (Folder 17)
      - Appropriations (Box 108., Folder 1)
      - Debts (Folder 2)
      - Referendum (Folder 3)
    - War and peace (Folder 4)
    - War Labor Board claims (Folder 5)
    - War profits bill (Folder 6)
    - Winona bridge (Folder 7)
    - WPA appropriations (Folder 8)
    - Youth (Folder 9)
    - Youth Act (Folder 10-11)
  - 1940. Continuation of previous series
    - General (Box 109., Folder 1)
    - Agriculture (Folder 2)
    - Air mail bases (Folder 3)
    - Alaska (Folder 4)
    - Aliens (Folder 5)
    - Allies (World War II) (Folder 6)
    - Annotations, Interstate Commerce Act (Folder 7)
    - Anti-trust laws (Folder 8)
    - Appropriations bill (Folder 9)
    - Army Band Masters bill (Folder 10)
    - Army legislation (Folder 11)
    - Army medical library (Folder 12)
    - Aviation (Folder 13)
    - Bald eagle, Protection of (Folder 14)
    - Bankhead-Jones Title 3 bill (Folder 15)
    - Barlow explosive experiment (Folder 16)
    - Books (talking books for the blind) (Folder 17)
    - Branch banking (Folder 18)
    - Bridges, Harry (Folder 19)
    - British seizure of mails (Folder 20)
    - Census questions (Folder 21)
    - Chain store bill (Folder 22)
    - Circuit judges (Folder 23)
    - Civil Aeronautics Authority (Folder 24)
    - Civil liberties (Box 110., Folder 1)
    - Civil service (Folder 2)
    - Civilian Conservation Corps (Folder 3)
    - Coal (Folder 4)
    - CIO legislative program (Folder 5)
    - Conscription (Folder 6)
    - Conscription of wealth (Folder 7)
    - Conservation (Folder 8)
    - Co-operatives (Folder 9)
    - Cotton (Folder 10)
    - Dies Committee (Folder 11)
    - Dumbarton House (Folder 12)
    - Education (Folder 13)
    - Farm loans (Folder 14)
    - Federal Credit Unions (Folder 15)
    - Federal Land Bank (Folder 16)
    - 5th column activities (Folder 17)
    - Finland (Folder 18)
    - Fishing, Commercial (Folder 19)
    - Flood control (Folder 20)
    - Food stamp plan (Box 111., Folder 1)
    - Foreign affairs (Folder 2)
    - Forest Service (Folder 3)
    - Fort Snelling Hospital (Folder 4)
    - Forum of the Air speech, 1940 June 25 (Folder 5)
    - Freight forwarders (Folder 6)
    - Gasoline tax (Folder 7)
    - Gold, Purchase of (Folder 8)
    - Government activities: Logan-Walter bill (Folder 9)
    - Government ownership of railroads (Folder 10)
    - Greenland (Folder 11)
    - Hatch bill (Folder 12)
    - Health (Folder 13)
    - Highway appropriations bills (Folder 14)
    - Hospital bill (Folder 15)
    - Housing (Folder 16)
    - Indian affairs (Folder 17)
    - Insurance (Folder 18)
    - Iron and steel export (Folder 19)
    - Islands (Folder 20)
    - Japanese aggression (Folder 21-22)
    - Judicial bill (Folder 23)
    - Kansas Pipe Line and Gas Company (Box 112., Folder 1-2)
    - Kings Canyon National Park (Folder 3)
    - Labor interests (Folder 4-5)
    - Lindbergh speech comments (Folder 6)
    - Liquor advertising on radio (Box 113., Folder 1)
    - Lynching laws (Folder 2)
    - Mail censorship (Folder 3)
    - Marketing dairy products (Folder 4)
    - Mexican products for sale (Folder 5)
    - Military training for boys (Folder 6)
    - Mining bill (Folder 7)
    - Mississippi River Parkway (Folder 8)
    - Mississippi (Upper) Water Transport (Folder 9)
    - Monetary (Folder 10)
    - Motion picture bill (Folder 11)
    - National Aviation Day (Folder 12)
    - National Defense (Folder 13)
    - National Guard (Folder 14)
    - National Youth Administration (Folder 15)
    - Panama Canal (Folder 16)
    - Preparedness (war) (Folder 17)
    - Radio station WDGY (Folder 18)
    - Refugee children (Folder 19)
    - Rio Grande Valley (Folder 20)
    - Rivers and harbors (Folder 21)
    - Safety (travel) (Folder 22)
    - St. Lawrence Waterway (Folder 23)
    - Salary reduction (Folder 24)
    - Sand, Andrew G. (Folder 25)
    - Seed and Feed Loan cancellation (Folder 26)
    - Social Justice article, April 1940 (Folder 27)
    - Sob stories
      - General (Folder 28)
      - Old age pensions (Folder 29)
      - Veterans (Folder 30)
      - WPA (Folder 31)
    - Social Security (Box 114., Folder 1)
    - Social Security Act (Folder 2)
    - Special delivery messengers (Folder 3)
    - Stimson-Knox appointments (Folder 4)
    - Stream pollution (Folder 5)
    - Sugar (Folder 6)
    - Taxes, business
      - General (Folder 7)
      - Food (Folder 8)
      - Highway user and motor (Folder 9)
      - Salary (Folder 10)
    - Teachers pensions (Folder 11)
    - Telegraph merger (Folder 12)
    - Television (Folder 13)
    - Text books (Folder 14)
    - Third party (Folder 15)
    - Third term (Folder 16)
    - Townsend Act (Folder 17)
    - Townsend bill (repeal of Silver Act) (Folder 18)
    - Trade agreements (Folder 19)
    - Transportation (Folder 20)
    - Unemployment compensation (Folder 21)
    - United States Housing Administration (Folder 22)
    - Vatican representation (Box 115., Folder 1)
    - Venereal diseases (Folder 2)
    - Veterans (Folder 3)
    - Veterans Administration (Fort Snelling Hospital) (Folder 4)
    - Veterans compensation (Folder 5)
    - Wagner Health bill (Folder 6)
    - War (Folder 7)
      - Contracts (Folder 8)
      - Debts (Folder 9)
      - Referendum (Folder 10)
    - Wayzata post office transfer (Folder 11)
    - Wheeler-Jones-La Follette bill (Folder 12)
    - Widows and orphans bill (Folder 13)
    - Workers Alliance legislative program (Folder 14)
    - Works Projects Administration (Box 116., Folder 1)
      - Opposition to (Folder 2)
    - Yearbooks mailed (Folder 3)
    - Yearbooks to be mailed (Box 117., Folder 1)
    - Unsorted (Folder 2-4)
  - 1937-1940. Constituent mail filed under name of correspondent and unsorted within each letter of the alphabet
    - A (Box 118., Folder 1-11)
    - A publications (Box 119., Folder 1)
    - B-Bo (Folder 2-8)
    - Br-Ca (Box 120., Folder 1-7)
    - Ce-Cz (Box 121., Folder 1-8)
    - C publications (Box 122., Folder 1)
    - D publications (Folder 2-10)
    - E (Box 123., Folder 1-5)
    - Fa-Fi (Folder 6-8)
    - Fl-F publications (Box 124., Folder 1-6)
    - G-Go (Folder 7-10)
    - Gr-G publications (Box 125., Folder 1-4)
    - Ha (Folder 5-7)
    - He-H publications (Box 126., Folder 1-9)
    - H publications (Box 127., Folder 1)
    - I (Folder 2-6)
    - Ja-Johnson (Folder 7-12)
    - Ju-J publications (Box 128., Folder 1-2)
    - K (Folder 3-7)
    - La (Folder 8)
    - La-L publications (Box 129., Folder 1-8)
    - Mc-Mi (Box 130., Folder 1-7)
    - Mi (Box 131., Folder 1)
    - Minneapolis (Folder 2)
    - Minnesota (Folder 3)
    - Mo-M publications (Folder 4-7)
    - Na (Box 132., Folder 1)
    - National (Folder 2)
    - Ne-N publications (Folder 3-9)
    - O (Box 133., Folder 1-7)
    - Pa-Ph (Folder 8-11)
    - Pi-P publications (Box 134., Folder 1-6)
    - Q-Q publications (Folder 7-8)
    - Ra-Re (Folder 9-10)
    - Ri-R publications (Box 135., Folder 1-7)
    - Sa-Se (Folder 8-11)
    - Sh-St (Box 136., Folder 1-12)
    - Su-S publications (Box 137., Folder 1-5)
    - T-T publications (Folder 6-11)
    - U-We (Box 138., Folder 1-5)